i have been waiting
a long time
for impulse to get online and he's
finally here
i just really need to drink this potion
for safety
boom
we're gone
so here is my secret base everybody
that's right did you think i could trust
you i know i know you can't see me just
pretend like my face is here i've
bamboozled you i've bamboozled impulse
and now it's time to mess with him some
more i just need to get out of here he
can't see me but he is
in the secret base so now oh here we go
i've prepared a little party room for
him
pesky bird pesky bird pesky bird pesky
bird no i just need to hide here
for him to find it
he found he found my secret viewing
space
oh no oh he's gonna see me i need to
make sure he's gonna see some particles
where is he i want him to find the pesky
bird room that's what i want here he
comes here comes he comes he found it
he's found it
[Laughter]
this is the best thing ever and he
doesn't even know that i'm right here
and now we run
oh man okay now i need to go back into
my secret base i keep working on it
don't buy me just got to work on my base
he said how on earth did you get these
birds in here without me noticing with
great effort
that's how it was a lot of work getting
these in
i don't know if you know this but
impulse has literally been digging this
hole for two days and i haven't been
able to log on this server without him
being here so making a secret base
inside impulse's base has been a little
bit of a challenge
he played it again this is this may be
the best room on hermitcraft well the
hidden base chronicles begin
this has only just begun
[Laughter]
you ready for a big
reveal
three two
one
and i'm back
boom hello
and
just like that
i'm gone welcome home
oh impulse you have no idea what's begun
no idea
well
i think i've probably been bamboozling
impulse more than enough i've been
adding
some small little things here and there
that are basically just red herrings i i
don't think he's found all of them he's
already found some of the ones that i've
put here i put like a sign saying
bamboozled over here and there's one
round the corner here as well
which is a pesky bird i guess there is
something in here so i'm just gonna keep
taunting him with loads of fake little
additions to his base
and i'm pretty sure that he's not gonna
find my secret base in here any time
soon this one has officially been
deserted it is not the real base and it
was never intended to be
it was a
156 iq play that's what i'm gonna call
it i never intended to stay here it was
all a ruse it was all a setup to get
impulse to know what i was up to and to
see if you guys could keep a secret you
firmly cannot i can tell you that for
nothing i i don't impulse this video i
saw it there was
many
many comments
spoiled it and
i think with that
there's not a lot to do especially while
impulse is not online so we'll leave our
secret base a mystery for now and we're
gonna try and expand it
day by day and see what we can get away
with for now though i do have a very
large personal order that was placed at
the barge by corrales he asked for 10
shulker boxes full of i mean i've just
been cleared out completely look at this
this is why the barge does so well i've
been absolutely cleared out he asked for
10 shulker boxes of sand and 10 of
gravel and then whatever andersite i
have as well so i'm i'm already out of
this i'm
i'm gonna have to go and do a little bit
of grinding for this order because i
have officially run out of that stock so
let's quickly go and get our shovel out
oh that's
quickly go
before they eat me
[Music]
okay this is what i've got i've got my
order together for corrales
all i need to do now is well deliver it
i've ended up becoming a bit of a
delivery boy recently and this is
definitely going to be a pesky bird
delivery now if you're ever traveling
with a pet unfortunately you have to
stop every now and again to let your pet
spawn to you because if you fly too far
away from your pet obviously the bird is
there staying there it's not gonna
teleport with me until
i land on a block and if you're too far
away
the pet doesn't come with you and i
think i probably went a little bit too
far
hey
these i'm out
no i'm out i don't i don't need you
right so we need to go to corrales base
take pesky bird with us and get this
order delivered
well
butter my biscuit
look at that
i did not know that this was being
worked on i am i'm loving the shading on
this
very cool
i think that might be x's um brewing
area right we are over here
at corrales's
base
city it's not really a base is it it's a
city corrales city the question is where
do we drop the delivery in a place that
he'll see it's been a little while since
i've done a pesky bird delivery i'm
surprised people don't take advantage of
it more often large orders delivered
straight to your door set pb pesky bird
on top
nice and there we have it our first
pesky bird delivery in absolutely ages
and now i need to work out how much
how much corrales needs to pay me but uh
i think he can afford it
if you know what i mean this man's
office is made out of literal diamonds i
had to get my calculator out for this
one right we got pb delivery 10 shulkers
of sand gravel and 1.5 of andersite now
i did total this up as if he was going
to buy it from the barge itself
and not including the boxes that came to
279 diamonds which sounds like an awful
lot so i gave a 10 diamond discount and
i said please play
please pay 269 diamonds to the barge and
please return the boxes i'm really
running low on these boxes so it'd be
good if he could give those back so
personal delivery from pb himself and we
should be getting a nice bulk payment
and i know that the reason that corrales
wants these is because he's using an
enormous amount of concrete i mean look
look all of this is concrete
and i think this is where he ran out
so i can see why he needs such a huge
order and it was my pleasure taking the
time to put it together but instead of
fueling other people's projects i think
it's important that we go and sort out
some of our own projects i've been
working out my design
for the interior of the mansion and
while i haven't got every single thing
figured out quite yet
i do know at least what i want to do
in the middle here i want to have a
giant fireplace i want to have big
pillars i want you to come in and go wow
so that's what we're going to do we're
going to create a wow
[Music]
all right so now we're going to hop into
a time lapse where
my goodness it feels really strange but
we're gonna do the interior of the base
and there's big plans for it big plans
let's
go
[Music]
[Applause]
here we go the interior of the mansion
take a look obviously we're not done
there is so much more to do but you know
in a project like this when you've got
an interior that looks a lot like that
sometimes the hardest part is just
placing those first few blocks
and my goodness have we done that i
think we've made really good progress
today it might it might only represent
20 odd seconds in the video
but this took three to four hours now
while i was building this i kept hearing
a ding like a bell or a note block or
something going on which i don't have
any of those in my base so i can only
assume that someone's gone and done
something so i i i'm going to hang out
here for a little longer it only
happened every
yeah really infrequently now i am going
to perform one of the biggest minecraft
flexes in the world now that is not
meant to be black stone that is meant to
be diamond but i'm so rich i can just
scaffold out of diamonds
means nothing to me so i am going to
replace this with actually
another i'm gonna flex even harder i'm
gonna scaffold with diamonds to make a
netherright block to put as my feature
centerpiece here
yep this is just how i scaffold now
that's how rich i am i can probably add
a few little bit of like richard e's in
here so maybe a diamond block in here
just to just to kind of flex on this
wealth and keep an ear out for those
dings or whatever they were so let's
briefly talk about my thought process
here because you might have some
questions why are there giant holes in
the ceiling might be number one on your
list well
they're supposed to be windows
okay
and with glass there admittedly from the
inside they look pretty good from the
outside
they
don't so much look at this
it does not look good it just looks
broken and unfinished so i have a bit of
a dilemma i either put windows in here
and add some sort of structure to it
make it look normal
or i remove the windows and just have it
all in prismarine now the problem with
that is that if i remove this window
what
this block doesn't want to break
okay
cool the problem is if i keep this
window i get all of the natural light
and since the sun is about to go down
and b dubs isn't online to say anything
about it we're about you're about to see
like how dark it gets in this room and
boy does it get dark i mean i've had to
spam torches because another issue i've
had is no matter what i do
there are just mobs spawning everywhere
look at this i mean this is
look at that that's a lot of diamonds so
you can see how kind of dark it gets
around here when it's nice and so take
sort of take that in for a second
because when i sleep boom you get so
much more natural light in here and it
does make a huge difference so i'm still
deciding on this and i want to say a big
thank you to pearlescent moon who
actually gave me a little hand trying to
put this together because uh i was very
much up against the clock on this one
like mobs everywhere where are they
hiding
there
i haven't heard any bings or tings so i
think we might be okay i actually when i
made this mansion i firmly knew about
all of this warped stuff coming up in
the nether so when i designed it i
wanted this fireplace from day one
and now i finally
get to actually put it together with
some soul campfires and some soul sand
and some smoke and this this moment has
kind of been brewing for a long time so
i'm very very happy about it i want to
make sure that it's taller here at the
back
than it is at the front to get the full
effect so i think that also means oh i
forgot to mention this there's an
appreciation gift for being an awesome
customer impulse's guardian goodies
which is really ironic that it came from
impulse because uh
i kind of you know
i'm squatting in his base
and it actually came in super handy for
this build so thank you very much
impulse that's very kind of you and i
think it's also time to get rid of this
as well
i just heard it
i just heard it and it definitely came
from this side of the room i was looking
for something and then i heard it that
was different to the one i heard earlier
that one went ding ding
this is gonna drive me mad now i know
there's see my base
is got loads of like hidden areas i mean
look at this i didn't even know this was
here oh my goodness
okay at least we know i'm not going
crazy there's some ding dings going
somewhere
okay that was a different ding ding
there's so many ding dings ding dongs
going
someone's someone's pranking my doorbell
someone's ringing a doorbell that i
didn't build and they're not even
running away that someone's pranked me
by building me a doorbell is that a new
game
going to houses that don't have a
doorbell giving them a doorbell ringing
the doorbell
and then running
okay
we're gonna get to the bottom of this
after a long search it doesn't seem like
i'm able to find the various
ding-donging that's going on however
this thing here mumbo's base because i
work at the mansion so much recently
i've sort of been in and around this
area i've been loading mumbo's base
and much like a cat on the street that
doesn't belong to you i've been feeding
it
it's kind of like this it's this stray
bass that i've been keeping alive
because i've been i've been loading it
up and
i don't know if mumbo's been feeding it
regularly enough
but um i i decided to start feeding it
so that um so that it doesn't die on him
because uh i'm i it's actually me that's
loading it up quite a lot of the time
it eats golden apples right there we go
oh
i wish he was able to add like a
crunch sound for his base like
you see if my base had a heartbeat it
would drive me absolutely insane
actually my bass kinda does have a
heartbeat now it keeps dinging at me
right i've had a quick look at my
comments see if there's any shenanigans
going on and as much as i am not on
board with spoilers
uh
once you've seen a spoiler you then know
the spoiler and you can't act like you
don't know the spoiler i shouldn't have
looked i'm never looking at my comments
again but uh i've i've heard impulse has
made a base and i've
impulses made a base in my base now as a
retaliation for me making a secret base
in his base there's a lot of base
building going on
so apparently and i looked at his video
it's directly under here
oh no
oh no it's the uno reverse bamboozle it
was here
and there's the ding i can't believe it
no okay we're gonna get rid of this but
i could have sworn that his base was
here as well
hold on i'm gonna look at his video
again because this makes no sense
yeah so in his video
you can see this
and then there's a tunnel
around here somewhere that goes to his
base like he's got he's got a massive
room
huge room it should be
right here in his video he walks
straight through here
down this corridor we'll get rid of more
of these dings
how many of those ding machines has he
made and
it should be
here
it shouldn't be too difficult to find if
it's that big
i'm a little bit worried about this sign
here
i've now spent 15 minutes digging around
and i've not found
anything not so much
as a little impulse sign of any kind
there's no corridor i followed exactly
where he went on his video and it leads
to a dead end so unless he's got some
sort of like
redstone door somewhere
i have to conclude
that i have been thoroughly bamboozled
but i'm not quite sure
what's going on
i think the games have just begun
they really have the mind games have
thoroughly begun
ah
man he's got me going in circles he's my
own lineup i just heard another ding how
many
okay maybe the ding machines are meant
to lead me somewhere
he can't have done this recently because
i've been working on this for the last
day so this must have been a while ago
also under here right i have got a huge
space now the plan for this area is tip
top secret okay but there is enough
space here for me to build an extra
secret space room here as well
oh my there's the i found it
i found it and that would explain why it
took so long
because when the cactus grows
it then activates and then hits
hits the bell
that's a very smart little clock there
and also i'm realizing the scale of how
difficult it's gonna be
to find a secret base in my base look at
all this just dead space
and it's just all hidden
okay that's the third ding dong machine
i found
i'm wondering if there's any more
i've also just got a random hop my base
is a blimming mess and i've even added
more holes in the back
oh dear this is gonna be a lot of work
but anyway i do want to know what you
guys think of this interior i think it's
off to a fantastic start i'm looking
forward to to really buckling down and
getting this as good as it could
possibly be we're about 10 done this is
the last time i believe my comments by
the way because i i'm i'm now thoroughly
convinced there's nothing here i have
checked
and there is just nothing here
there is just absolutely nothing
i've checked in all directions i've gone
backwards and forwards through all the
nooks and crannies and there's there's
just nothing here
we need more information we're going to
need more information or i could just
tear up the whole of the underground of
my base but i don't think that's a very
good use of my time i just received a
message that my payment is at the barge
and i need to go and pick it up
i love diamonds
i just why did i walk out of the portal
actually i've been wondering for a while
now i have a lot of diamonds there it is
thank you
i have a lot of diamonds right but i'm
not actually sure what to do with them
do i make my own diamond throne do i
hang them somewhere like make a diamond
chandelier i need some ideas what do i
do with this ludicrous amount of
diamonds and we're about to add to it as
well
there we go and we got all of our
shulker boxes back thank you very much
corrales pleasure doing business with
you and we add a cool half a stack of
diamond blocks to our collection wow
there's actually if someone's been busy
there's a lot of diamonds in here
actually
oh my goodness
i'm gonna have to do a big restocking
session again it's so hard to keep up
with the barge sometimes oh my goodness
okay i love the barge we had another bit
look at that
we're literally rolling in it i say
literally it's the the opposite of
literally you can't really roll you you
can't roll or can you roll well now i
know what i got to do
diamonds
rolling in it
close enough
what on earth is this
when the countdown ends it begins how
there's some very sh how have they done
this crazy text
whoa
um someone's up to some shenanigans okay
right let's take this in for a second is
this the new button
this looks exactly like the button
i'm so up for another button
is there a button to press thank
goodness we don't have fire spread on
this server insert name be part of
change
oh there's so many of these
when the countdown ends it begins
give us your name
insert name these are these look like
they're all the same insert name be part
of change what does this one say change
is coming well that's not ominous it
doesn't look like there is a button but
it does look like the button has crashed
down from space
hence the crater does anyone know what
this is about normally i would go ahead
and just press a button without thinking
about it but
i don't actually know what this is and
there doesn't seem to be any more
information
than just change
hcbbs
hermitcraft big
brian society
hermitcraft it's got to be hermitcraft
right hc hermitcraft
big bingo start
i don't know i'm probably gonna regret
this but
let's just let's do it let's add our
name oh wow
how did they get this this text format
rename and insert in chest oh my
my my my text doesn't look very good
[Laughter]
that's
that's that's what i'm going with
that's yeah that's it green
and that's the closest i can get to a
weird name oh it beat oh my goodness
it gave me uh it gave me a little bit of
gold
you are invited to the changeover
well on that bombshell
quite literally
i think that's where we're gonna have to
end this episode
uh i'm invited to the changeover so i
wonder how long
this thing is gonna go on for there's
already two lights gone
i don't know how i don't know when this
got here or who built it if anyone knows
who built this let me know because i
have not seen anything about this so far
but um
we're signed up i don't know who else is
signed up i don't know what this is why
did i do this can i up down if it's if
if it's bad if it's bad i'm just not
gonna do it i'm a you know i'm an
independent hermit i'll do what i want
anyway i shall see you in the next
episode
bye